export default [{
  question: "I think we have a huge fun deficit. And we need to figure out how to fill that fun deficit.",
  answer: "Hillary Clinton"
}, {
  question: "I've watched a lot of cats do a lot of weird and interesting things.",
  answer: "Hillary Clinton"
},{
  question: "The thing about youth culture is... I don't understand it.",
  answer: "Leslie Knope"
}, {
  question: "It's not over until the lady in the pantsuit says it is.",
  answer: "Hillary Clinton"
}, {
  question: "What I hear when I'm being yelled at is people caring really loudly at me.",
  answer: "Leslie Knope"
}, {
  question: "My two secrets to staying healthy: wash your hands all the time, and the other is hot peppers. I eat a lot of hot peppers.",
  answer: "Hillary Clinton"
}, {
  question: "We have to remember what's really important in life: friends, waffles, and work.",
  answer: "Leslie Knope"
}, {
  question: "Europe is a miracle.",
  answer: "Hillary Clinton"
}, {
  question: "I'm not even a human being. I was constructed in a garage in Palo Alto a very long time ago.",
  answer: "Hillary Clinton"
}, {
  question: "I guess some people object to powerful depictions of awesome ladies.",
  answer: "Leslie Knope"
}, {
  question: "I find it relaxing and entertaining and informative, watching HGTV.",
  answer: "Hillary Clinton"
} ]